<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Digital Tijori</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bottom_navigation">HomeActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_edit_bank_account">AddEditBankAccountActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_detailed_bank_account">DetailedBankAccount</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_edit_card">AddEditCardActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_edit_credential">AddEditCredentialActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_detailed_credential">DetailedCredentialActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_detailed_card">DetailedCardActivity</string>

    <string name="feedback_email">developer.harsh.nandwani@gmail.com</string>

    <string name="about_app_content">
Digital Tijori lets you store your bank accounts, cards and credentials. So that its easily accessible to you.
\n\nEvery information stored here is sensitive and following things are ensured to make users trust the app
\n\n1) No secrets! Digital Tijori is a completely opensource project, the source code is open for all to see on Github.
\n\n2) Digital Tijori DOES NOT connect to internet. So all the data is on your local app storage.
\nHow to verify?
\n\nYou can check Digital Tijori\'s Data usage in your phone\'s settings -> apps -> Digital Tijori, the data usage will always be 0.
\n\nFor an android app to use Internet it must declare that it uses Internet in AndroidManifest.xml file, otherwise the app cannot use/connect to Internet at all.
\nDigital Tijori does not declare this and it can be verified by checking the source code of Digital Tijori on Github.
</string>


    <string name="backup_description">
        Digital Tijori uses Advanced Encryption Standard (AES-256) for encrypting which is one of the most strongest encryption algorithm. This encryption is done on your device locally.
        \n\nThis is how backup works:
        \n -> You enter a secret key which is hashed with SHA-256.
        \n -> The hash is then used to encrypt your sensitive data with AES-256 algorithm.
        \n -> The encrypted data is save to .txt file which is safe to share and store.

    </string>

    <string name="url_to_github_repo">https://github.com/HarshNandwani/Digital-Tijori</string>

    <string name="url_to_manifest_file_source">https://github.com/HarshNandwani/Digital-Tijori/blob/main/app/src/main/AndroidManifest.xml</string>

</resources>
